Sheinkman, Jack Collection of Audio-Visual Materials 6097 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jack Sheinkman Collection of Audio-Visual Materials
1993-1997
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
6097 AV
3.78 cubic feet
3.8 linear ft.
Audiovisual material.
5794421
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
VGV 2/99, March 14, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 19, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619: ACWA Records 5619 C-S MB: ACTWU President Jack Sheinkman Additional Books, Memorabilia, and Files 5619 C-S: ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Files [Deaccessioned] 5619/004: ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Files
Labor unions -- United States; Labor leaders -- United States; Transport workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Sheinkman, Jacob; Amalgamated Bank of New York; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; American Jewish World Service; International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers; International Chemical Workers' Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Labor Institute of Public Affairs; National Labor Committee for Eduction and Human Rights; United Mine Workers of America
5794421
- ACTWU Convention Video - 1993, 1 (Box 1)
- Meet the Press - Joint appearance of Tom Donahue and John Sweeney, 1995; 2 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  aired Sept. 3, 1995
- If You don't Come in on SundayDon't Come in on Monday, 3 (Box 1)
- Mirrors of the Heart: Race and Identity, 4 (Box 1)
- Reaffirming Our Purpose - March 22, 1996, 5 (Box 1)
- Introducing Achieving Breakthrough Service, 6 (Box 1)
- The American Experience, 7 (Box 1)
- Did They Buy It?, 8 (Box 1)
- Out of Darkness: the Mine Workers' Story, 9 (Box 1)
- Teamwork Day 1996, 10 (Box 1)
- Trans. Workers Union "Stop Kawasaki", 1988; 11 (Box 1)
  11/8/1988
- ACTWU in Action, 12 (Box 1)
- Jesse Jackson ACTWU - 6/28/1995, 13 (Box 1)
- The Golden Door, 14 (Box 1)
- Hard Copy - three part series on Nicaraguan sweatshops - Nov. 1997, 15 (Box 1)
- It's Time for Change Paul Filson for Manager, 16 (Box 1)
- Mattan the Carpet, Kort Version, 17 (Box 1)
- If you don't come in on SundayDon't come in on Monday, 18 (Box 1)
- ACTWU - The Inheritance, 19 (Box 1)
- 1993 ACTWU Convention, 20 (Box 1)
- 1989 AFL-CIO Convention - Nov. 13-16, 1989, 21 (Box 1)
- United Auto Workers "No Power Greaterthe Hand of Solidarity", 22 (Box 1)
- The Golden Door / presented by the New York Joint Board, ACTWU, 23 (Box 1)
- Highlights of 1989 AFL-CIO Convention, 24 (Box 1)
- Leaving Home: We do the work, 25 (Box 1)
- Profiles of America Featuring January 22, 1995, 26 (Box 1)
- Amalgamated Clothing & Textile Workers Union - Philadelphia Joint Board, Workers' Bill of Rights Demonstration, September 16, 1987, 27 (Box 1)
- Haiti: Killing the Dream, 28 (Box 1)
- Crafted with Pride in the U.S.A. Council: Quick Response in Action, 29 (Box 1)
- Sweet Harmony, 30 (Box 1)
- Afternoon Edition Segment, 31 (Box 1)
- Zoned for Slavery, 32 (Box 1)
- The Killing Floor, 33 (Box 1)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 2)
- Jack Sheinkman - ILGWU, ACTWU, Bill Clinton, 2 (Box 2)
- ACTWU/Jack Sheinkman Convention Program, 3 (Box 2)
- McNeil-Lehrer news Hour 8/17/1995 -- Edited version, 4 (Box 2)
- BCTD Jack Sheinkman, 5 (Box 2)
- Jack/McNeal Lehrer - 2/23/1993, 6 (Box 2)
- ACTWU - Keynote Address Jack Sheinkman - 6/28/1995, 7 (Box 2)
- Challenge of the Unemployed Suzuka Fuji Xerox, 8 (Box 2)
- ACTWU / Jack Sheinkman Convention Program, 9 (Box 2)
  U-Matic S not VHS
- ILGWU, Jack Sheinkman - 6/26/1995, 10 (Box 2)
  Dub
- 1993 ACTWU - 6th Constitutional Convention - Jack Sheinkman, President, ACTWU, 11 (Box 2)
- AMTEX Signing Ceremony, 12 (Box 2)
- Press Conf. with Governor Mario Cuomo at Pietrafesa Facility - Long version -- 3/10/1994, 13 (Box 2)
- Goodwill Games - Best Intentions Bergman, Goodwill Games, 14 (Box 2)
- The Great Depression - Part I, II, III, 15 (Box 2)
- Evy Duty, 16 (Box 2)
- Working America, 17 (Box 2)
- Clinton Speech to UNITE, 18 (Box 2)
- Radios Second Opinion interview Jack Sheinkman, 19 (Box 2)
- Nicaragua/Elsalva, 20 (Box 2)
- Jack Sheinkman: 1995 ACTWU Convention, Miami, Florida, 21 (Box 2)
- The Challenge & The Promise: Investing in People, 22 (Box 2)
- Teamwork '91 - Jack Sheinkman, 23 (Box 2)
- ACORN - Interview with Jack Sheinkman, 2/25/91, 1991; 1 (Box 4)
- NRF - 1993 Annual Convention / International Seminar Keynote: Building a New America, 1 (Box 5)
- Anne Feeney and Friends: United We Bargain, Divided We Beg!, 1 (Box 6)
- An Example of: Broadening Labor's Message the UMWA Pittston Campaign, 1 (Box 7)
- Hightower Radio - Eye on Newt -- 2/4, 2/18, 2/21, 2/25, 3/11/95, 1995; 1 (Box 8)
- Louisville Speech 10/90, 1990; 1 (Box 9)
- America and the World: A conversation with Stanley Hoffmann on American Foreign Policy in a World Transformed, October 18, 1990, 1 (Box 10)
- American Jewish World Service: partners for Change - 12/18/1987, 1 (Box 3)
- The Road to Dignity - organizing - by UFCW, 2 (Box 3)
- OKI Factory Automation, 3 (Box 3)
- Nelson Mandela Visits the AFL-CIO, June 25, 1990, 4 (Box 3)
- Josh Karan - Public Issue Films, Working for Change: Allen, Divoky, Schwartz: Profiles, 5 (Box 3)
- Dateline - 12/22/1992 -- Walmart and Overseas Buying (USA Campaign), 6 (Box 3)
- Ted Koppel Report: Tragedy at Tiananmen -- 3/8/1990, 7 (Box 3)
- Communication Workers of America - Tough 'N Together, 8 (Box 3)
- Separate but equal -- Poitier & Burt Lancaster, 9 (Box 3)
- Toshiba Satellite: Series Training Tape, 10 (Box 3)
- Gospel Seder: An interfaith Jewish/African-American/Christian Passover Freedom Service-Part I "Sweet Harmony", 11 (Box 3)
- Hunsar Project: American Jewish World Service, 12 (Box 3)
- Ed Luck on Larry King Live -- 6/21/1993, 13 (Box 3)
- J. Sheinkman: ICWU conv. Address - 10/18/1988, 14 (Box 3)
- ACTWU: Jack Sheinkman: Interview and Speech, 15 (Box 3)
- Jack Sheinkman meets Nelson Mandela, 16 (Box 3)
- J. Sheinkman, 17 (Box 3)
- Sheinkman Tribute video, 18 (Box 3)
- American Jewish World Service Armero -- 11/12/1986, 19 (Box 3)
- American Jewish World Service - AJWS in the Philippines, 20 (Box 3)
- The Dream Continues, 21 (Box 3)
- The Captain's Paradise, 22 (Box 3)